<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[gzruby]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/"/>
  <updated>2012-07-13T00:05:31+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.gzruby.org/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[gzruby]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 18 - Come to gzruby Meetup #7]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/07/12/july-18-gzruby-meetup-number-7/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-12T17:40:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/07/12/july-18-gzruby-meetup-number-7</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>OK ruby fans, its that time again! Another 2 months have gone by&#8230;what have you learned? Did you try any new gems? Did you start using any new tools?</p>

<p>Since we met last, what&#8217;s been going on: we&#8217;ve got the <a href="https://gist.github.com/2838490">epic comment thread about code design</a>, we&#8217;ve got <a href="http://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2012/06/29/ruby-1-8-7-p370-released/">the final bug-fix release for 1.8.7</a> (Have you updated to 1.9.3 yet?), and we&#8217;ve got some SQL injection updates for <a href="http://weblog.rubyonrails.org/2012/6/12/ann-rails-3-2-6-has-been-released/">Rails in v3.2.6</a>.</p>

<p>Lets get together and celebrate our ruby family!</p>

<h4>时间/When: July 18, 7:30 PM</h4>

<h4>地点/Where: <a href="http://gz.o.cn/13105">Kudelabs 明月一路59号, 汉苑 西塔601</a></h4>

<h4>地铁/Metro: <a href="http://www.exploregz.com/metro/pedia/station/wuyangcun/">五羊村A出口/Line 5 - Wu Yang Cun, Exit A</a></h4>

<p>希望到时能见到你的身影！如果你有什么好的想法，发到<a href="http://groups.google.com/groups/gzruby">邮件列表</a>告诉我们吧!</p>

<p>We look forward to seeing you there! If you have any topic ideas or plans, let us know on the <a href="http://groups.google.com/groups/gzruby">mailing list</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes from Meetup 6]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/05/29/notes-from-meetup-6/"/>
    <updated>2012-05-29T15:30:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/05/29/notes-from-meetup-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://www.gzruby.org/images/meetup6.png" style="width: 800px" alt="We &lt;3 Ruby!" title="Join us every other month!" /></p>

<p>I think we can all agree that the meeting held May 16, 2012 was one of our best yet. We had a bunch of new visitors. Its thrilling to see young rubyists joining our ranks, and at this meeting we had 5 recent graduates who all learned ruby on their own. We also love to see visitors from other platforms, we welcome anyone who has a passion for technology and software development.</p>

<p>At this meeting we had the honor of hosting guests from China Telecom. They were looking to find the next great mobile app and learn about what current mobile app developers are thinking about. Visitors of all types are welcome - from different disciplines and different platforms. Developers don&#8217;t work in a vaccum, we need to work together with others to make sure our products get out into the world.</p>

<p>Thanks again to <a href="http://weibo.com/strandbeer">Strand Beer</a> for the wonderful refreshment!</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Namespace-less Rails Engines <a href="http://github.com/shaokun/nl-engine/">http://github.com/shaokun/nl-engine/</a></strong></p>

<p>As we develop more and more applications, we find ways to make our life easier and start to re-use parts of an app in the next project. Hopefully, as time goes on, we can build reusable components that we can use in future apps to speed up development. In static, client side developemnt, this kind of code reuse is common and easily accomplished. In web development, when dealing with server side code, HTML, javascript and databases, it can get complicated. As of Rails 3.x Engines are very handy and a great way to share code between apps. But you don&#8217;t want exactly the same code in every project. Sometimes one client wants to be able to delete widgets, another client wants to edit widgets, and a third client wants to be able to copy her widgets. So the next question is, how do we share common code between apps, and use ruby&#8217;s object oriented nature to extend functionality.</p>

<p>In his talk, Shaokun described a technique to make sharing code easier by building Rails Engines that can be overridden cleanly. The engine code is kept seperate and any custom functionality is implemented at the project level. Your engine can live in a git submodule, and all of your custom code - model, controller, and views - lives in your current project. This separation makes it easy to continue to maintain the core functionality while being able to satisfy each client&#8217;s needs.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="https://github.com/shaokun">伍少坤</a></p></li>
<li><p><strong>Angular.js <a href="http://angularjs.org/">http://angularjs.org/</a> (<a href="http://igorminar.github.com/ng-slides/angular-intro/index.html">slides</a>)</strong></p>

<p>Rails is a great framework for the server side. It gives you a well-defined structure and lots of tools for managing data and code on the server. Yet modern web apps have matured to the point where much of the interesting parts of the app are on the client side. On this side Rails shows some weakness - you need to mix several languages, js, css, html, erb into templates that are compiled server-side and then sent to the browser fully-baked. In today&#8217;s world of highly interactive and dynamic web applications, the Rails way is simply no longer good enough.</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/angular/angular.js">Angular.js</a> is one of many projects attempting to fill in this gap. It is a way to manage client side view logic compltely in the browser using pure HTML and JS. Similar to projects like <a href="http://emberjs.com/">ember.js</a> and <a href="http://backbonejs.org/">backbone.js</a>, it allows you to define html templates and fill them with live data, either taken from a server or computed in the browser with user input.</p>

<p>Angular caught our attention because it integrates well with existing technologies, it doesn&#8217;t require you to move everything over at once. You can implement just part of a page in angular, if you wish, and change the rest slowly over time. It also has a very clean way of dealing with data from the server and integrating it into the page.</p>

<p>Paired with a strong server-side framework like <a href="https://github.com/IgorMinar/angularjs_rails_demo">Rails, Angular</a> could be the the missing piece. The piece that takes us into a new world of truly interactive, user friendly, web apps.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="https://github.com/adevadeh">@adevadeh</a></p></li>
</ul>


<hr />

<p>Thanks very much to our presenters for sharing. We really appreciate that you stood up to share what you&#8217;ve been working on or show us something that may help us in our daily work. We hold these meetings to learn from each other, so be sure to give yourself some time to show other developers what you have learned.</p>

<h3>See you at the next meeting, scheduled for Wed,  July 18, 2012</h3>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for Meetup #6/第六次聚会]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/05/11/time-for-meetup-number-6/"/>
    <updated>2012-05-11T18:43:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/05/11/time-for-meetup-number-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Ruby的乡亲父老们, 大家下午好哦! 距离上次的聚会快2个月的时间了, 这意味着, 我们又要见面了. 自从上次的聚会之后, Ruby社区又发布了一些新玩意, 像<a href="https://github.com/rails/rails/issues/5228">the mass-assignment security scandal</a>, <a href="http://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2012/04/20/ruby-1-9-3-p194-is-released/">Ruby 1.9.3-p194</a>, 和灰常有趣的<a href="http://www.rubymotion.com/">ruby-on-iOS</a>方法. 你在Ruby社区还发现了什么新玩意儿么? 咱们一起聊聊吧, 顺便和我们分享一下你在互联网开发的斗争史吧!</p>

<p>Good afternoon my good ruby compatriots! The third Wednesday of the second moon approaches, indicating that our time to gather is near. In the time since we&#8217;ve last met, some exciting new developments have surcfaced in the ruby community: <a href="https://github.com/rails/rails/issues/5228">the mass-assignment security scandal</a>, <a href="http://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2012/04/20/ruby-1-9-3-p194-is-released/">Ruby 1.9.3-p194</a>, and a very interesting <a href="http://www.rubymotion.com/">ruby-on-iOS solution</a>. What else have you seen in your ruby travels? Come, relax, share some fine ale and tell us your war stories from the world of web development.</p>

<h4>时间/When: May 16, 7:30 PM</h4>

<h4>地点/Where：<a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/place?q=%E5%B9%BF%E5%B7%9E+%E6%98%8E%E6%9C%88%E4%B8%80%E8%B7%AF+%E6%B1%89%E8%8B%91&amp;hl=en&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;cid=2763294127675392599">Kudelabs 明月一路59号, 汉苑 西塔601</a></h4>

<h4>地铁/Metro：<a href="http://www.exploregz.com/metro/pedia/station/wuyangcun/">五羊村A出口/Line 5 - Wu Yang Cun, Exit A</a></h4>

<p>希望到时能见到你的身影！如果你有什么好的想法，发到<a href="http://groups.google.com/groups/gzruby">邮件列表</a>告诉我们吧!</p>

<p>We look forward to seeing you there! If you have any topic ideas or plans, let us know on the <a href="http://groups.google.com/groups/gzruby">mailing list</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes from 第五聚会/meetup #5]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/05/09/notes-from-meetup-number-5/"/>
    <updated>2012-05-09T15:20:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/05/09/notes-from-meetup-number-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="images/meetup5.jpg" style="width: 800px" alt="Happy group members" title="Join us every other month!" /></p>

<p>OK, this is a bit late. The last gzruby meeting we held, on March 21, was a great success: we had visitors from Shenzhen and a <a href="http://twitter.com/#!/danielkehoe">Rails hero from the US</a>; we imbibed some <a href="http://www.weibo.com/strandbeer">great beer made by one of our members</a>; and to top it all off we had some really fun and exciting presentations.</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Working with Bootstrap <a href="http://twitter.github.com/bootstrap/">http://twitter.github.com/bootstrap/</a></strong></p>

<p>With Rails, we have a very stable and mature back-end framework that allows us to write code in a standard way. Bootstrap from Twitter provides a similar functionality for the front-end. Rather than rolling your own css again and again, bootstrap gives you a standard way to layout your HTML pages, a standard way to style buttons and other elements, and it is generally much better than anything you could come up with on your own.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="https://github.com/leondu">Leon Du</a> (<a href="http://www.slideshare.net/leondu/twitter-bootstrap-12949509">slides</a>)</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Introducing Web-App-Themes <a href="https://github.com/pilu/web-app-theme">https://github.com/pilu/web-app-theme</a></strong></p></li>
</ul>


<p> When starting a new app, we have to choose how to style it. We want it to look nice, but don&#8217;t want to spend time designing colors or write out tons of markup. Web App Themes takes care of this for us. But rather than an engine or an almost ready made app, it simply helps you generate HTML and CSS for you to use as you see fit. For certain projects where you just need to get started with some reasonable good looking HTML and CSS, Web App Themes may be your best option.</p>

<p>  Presented by <a href="https://github.com/shaokun">@shaokun</a></p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>The Wonders of Pry <a href="https://github.com/pry/pry">https://github.com/pry/pry</a></strong></p>

<p>Pry is an IRB replacement that will knock your socks off. William certianly knocked our socks off with his presentation! Imagine being able to treat your entire ruby process&#8217; object space like a simple filesystem, where you can travel down paths to inspect data, <code>cd ..</code> to go back, and search down another branch. You can even ask questions like &#8220;Which method on (this object) could give me (this result)?&#8221; If you are a ruby developer and haven&#8217;t seen pry, you need to give it a look.</p>

<p>To invoke pry in your rails app, just add the line: <code>(require pry; binding.pry) #!!</code></p>

<p>Presented by William</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Rails App Templates <a href="http://railsapps.github.com/">http://railsapps.github.com/</a></strong></p>

<p>The Rails ecosystem is full of choices, you&#8217;ve got gems and engines, fixture generators and testing frameworks. This can get overwhelming as technologies change fast. That&#8217;s where this project comes in. It attempts to provide up-to-date documentation on the latest best-practices with Rails. Whether its building apps that use Devise for authentication, or how to integrate bootstrap into Rails, Rails Apps has you covered. Check out their extensive list of template apps and detailed tutorials.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/danielkehoe">Daniel Kehoe</a></p></li>
</ul>


<hr />

<p>Thanks very much to our presenters for sharing. We really appreciate that you stood up to share what you&#8217;ve been working on or show us something that may help us in our daily work. We hold these meetings to learn from each other, so be sure to give yourself some time to show other developers what you have learned.</p>

<h3>See you at the next meeting, scheduled for Wed, May 16, 2012</h3>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[第五次聚会/Meetup #5]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/03/14/time-for-gzruby-meetup-number-5/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-14T17:12:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/03/14/time-for-gzruby-meetup-number-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Ruby开发者们，我们又来了！咱们小聚一下，分享过去这几个月我们在Ruby领域上面所关注的，学习的。瞧瞧，<a href="http://weblog.rubyonrails.org/2012/1/20/rails-3-2-0-faster-dev-mode-routing-explain-queries-tagged-logger-store/">Rails 3.2</a>发布了，还有<a href="http://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2012/02/16/ruby-1-9-3-p125-is-released/">ruby 1.9.3-p125</a> 和 <a href="http://spreecommerce.com/blog/2012/02/09/spree-1-0-0-released/">Spree 1.0</a>，在这里有许多很酷的东西值得我们去分享和讨论的。你还可以谈谈你在github上面有趣的项目，或者一些新颖的工具，或者一个帮助我们更快地coding的小技巧，我们都希望你能跟咱们分享！</p>

<p>Hey rubyists, its that time again. Time for us to gather, to celebrate, and to share what we&#8217;ve learned over the last few months. Lets see, <a href="http://weblog.rubyonrails.org/2012/1/20/rails-3-2-0-faster-dev-mode-routing-explain-queries-tagged-logger-store/">Rails 3.2</a> is out now, <a href="http://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2012/02/16/ruby-1-9-3-p125-is-released/">ruby 1.9.3-p125</a>, <a href="http://spreecommerce.com/blog/2012/02/09/spree-1-0-0-released/">Spree 1.0</a>, and of course the excellent <a href="http://reddotrubyconf.com/">RedDotRubyConf</a> - lots of cool stuff for us to look at and discuss. So think about your favorite github projects, any new tools you&#8217;ve come to love, or any tricks you&#8217;ve got that help you code faster, and come share with us.</p>

<h4>时间/When：March 21, 7:30 PM</h4>

<h4>地点/Where：<a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/place?q=%E5%B9%BF%E5%B7%9E+%E6%98%8E%E6%9C%88%E4%B8%80%E8%B7%AF+%E6%B1%89%E8%8B%91&amp;hl=en&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;cid=2763294127675392599">Kudelabs 明月一路59号, 汉苑 西塔601</a></h4>

<h4>地铁/Metro：<a href="http://www.exploregz.com/metro/pedia/station/wuyangcun/">五羊村A出口/Line 5 - Wu Yang Cun, Exit A</a></h4>

<p>希望到时能见到你的身影！如果你有什么好的想法，发到<a href="http://groups.google.com/groups/gzruby">邮件列表</a>告诉我们吧!</p>

<p>We look forward to seeing you there! If you have any topic ideas or plans, let us know on the <a href="http://groups.google.com/groups/gzruby">mailing list</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes From 第四聚会/Meetup #4]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/01/11/notes-from-the-4th-meeting/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-11T20:11:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/01/11/notes-from-the-4th-meeting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last Wednesday, Jan 11th we held our fourth meetup. Again, we had a wonderful time getting to know fellow rubyists. There were quite a few new faces, including <a href="http://haifengsoft.com">visitors from Denmark</a>, and new <a href="http://favoritemedium.com">members from Singapore</a>. We love to meet new people, so if you have friends or know anyone who may be interested, please bring them along next time.</p>

<p>As is our custom, we started the meeting with general introductions, then went into our talks for the evening. Here are some notes on the topics presented:</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Introducing <a href="http://www.gzruby.org">http://www.gzruby.org</a></strong></p>

<p>The official blog for gzruby. We plan to use the blog to record our meetings and as a landing page for Ruby and Rails in South China. As our organization grows, we hope people continue to find the blog and that makes it easier for them to find the group and come to a meeting. This is the site for our community, so please make suggestions or contribute directly. The source is on <a href="http://github.com/gzruby/gzruby.github.com">github</a>.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="http://github.com/adevadeh">@adevadeh</a></p></li>
<li><p><strong>Zero-config local servers - pow <a href="http://pow.cx">http://pow.cx</a></strong></p>

<p>This is a great way for developers and testers to run apps locally. Why not use <code>rails server</code> you may ask? Because rather than starting and stopping your app all the time, your <code>pow</code> server will just keep your app running. You don&#8217;t need to fuss about with ports, so it&#8217;s easy to run multiple apps at the same time. If you are working with any oauth APIs such as the Facebook API, you need a real domain name for your test app; <code>pow</code> gives you a really easy way to set that up. Don&#8217;t forget, you should also check out the <a href="http://pow.cx/manual.html#section_4"><code>pow</code> helper gems</a> to make things even easier.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="http://twitter.com/teohm">HuiMing</a></p></li>
<li><p><strong>The Joys of seed-fu <a href="https://github.com/mbleigh/seed-fu">https://github.com/mbleigh/seed-fu</a></strong></p>

<p>Making sure your Rails app has the right data to start things off can get really cumbersome. seed-fu helps make the process a little more streamlined and friendly. You can easily specify objects that need to be created and stored in your DB every time you start your app.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="http://weibo.com/huipingc">Kevin</a></p></li>
<li><p><strong>The Future of Personal Robotics <a href="assets/EmergingParadigms_Robotics.pdf">(slides)</a></strong></p>

<p>A very interesting talk indeed. We looked at where cheap robots are today, and what we could do to take them to the next level. We already have cheap robots that can move on their own, react to humans, and perform basic tasks. To expand the abilities of these robots, we could make the brain on the robot more sophisticated and expensive. But why not move the brain to the smartphone? This way we can add complex behaviors that interact with humans and the cloud. Robots from <a href="http://arexx.com.cn">http://arexx.com.cn</a> were demonstrated. Who knows, maybe soon we&#8217;ll have a <code>my_robot</code> gem that allows you to write apps to control a domestic helper robot.</p>

<p>Presented by <a href="http://cn.linkedin.com/in/chancejiang">Chance Jiang</a></p></li>
</ul>


<hr />

<p>Thanks very much to our presenters for sharing. We would like to encourage anyone to present at the next meeting. You can talk about anything you find interesting, or something you find useful in your work. By sharing with each other, we learn from each other, and we all become better developers.</p>

<h3>See you at the next meeting, scheduled for Wed, March 21, 2012</h3>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[join us for gzruby meetup #4]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/01/10/join-us-for-gzruby-meetup-number-4/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-10T10:03:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2012/01/10/join-us-for-gzruby-meetup-number-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>第四次聚会  Jan 11, 7:30 PM</h2>

<p>Hope we all had a great start to 2012!</p>

<p>Lets kick off the ruby year with a meeting. Note, we are moving the meeting from its normal time to accommodate the coming Spring Festival Holiday.</p>

<p>Look forward to seeing everyone there!</p>

<p>时间/When：11/1, 7:30 PM<br />
地点/Where：<a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/place?q=%E5%B9%BF%E5%B7%9E+%E6%98%8E%E6%9C%88%E4%B8%80%E8%B7%AF+%E6%B1%89%E8%8B%91&amp;hl=en&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;cid=2763294127675392599">Kudelabs 明月一路59号, 汉苑 西塔601</a><br />
地铁/Metro：<a href="http://www.exploregz.com/metro/pedia/station/wuyangcun/">五羊村A出口/Line 5 - Wu Yang Cun, Exit A</a><br /></p>

<p>Any topic ideas or plans, let us know on the mailing list.</p>

<h2>Wow, this is a large meeting! Thanks for coming everyone!</h2>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[第三次聚会/gzruby meetup #3]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2011/11/18/notes-from-the-3rd-gzruby-meetup/"/>
    <updated>2011-11-18T11:27:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2011/11/18/notes-from-the-3rd-gzruby-meetup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="images/seb_gzruby.jpeg" style="width: 800px" alt="Image of Seb with a slide" title="Seb explains his scaling methods" /></p>

<p>非常感谢大家抽空过来参加昨晚的<strong>gzruby</strong>聚会。不仅可以跟使用ruby的老友记们交流，而且也是一次认识新朋友的好机会。很高兴看到使用<strong>ruby</strong>的朋友越来越多，并且可以相互分享当中的快乐<br />
Thanks to everyone who attended the <strong>gzruby</strong> meetup last wednesday night. It was great to get a chance to meet up with our ruby friends and we also met a lot of new people. It‘s exciting to see how the community is growing as we gain new members and introduce more people to the joys of ruby.</p>

<p> 以下是大家的一些分享 / The presentations included:</p>

<ul>
<li>Launch of <strong><a href="http://gems.gzruby.org">http://gems.gzruby.org</a></strong>, the GZRUBY rubygems mirror</li>
<li><strong>Real Life Rails Scaling</strong>, by <a href="http://cn.linkedin.com/in/sebastianroth">Seb</a>. Scaling your app, your team, and yourself. (<a href="http://www.slideshare.net/SebastianRoth/rails-scaling">slides</a>)</li>
<li><strong>method_proxy</strong> - some fun with ruby&#8217;s dynamic programming, by <a href="http://github.com/jevgz">Jev</a>. A look at how we can utilize ruby&#8217;s meta-programming features to get deep insight into our code. (<a href="https://github.com/kudelabs/method_proxy">method_proxy sample code</a>, <a href="https://github.com/downloads/kudelabs/method_proxy/method_proxy-at-GZ-Ruby-Conf-Nov2011.odp">slides</a>)</li>
<li><strong>Cloud Service API design</strong>, by <a href="http://cn.linkedin.com/in/chancejiang">Chance Jiang</a></li>
</ul>


<p>让我们一起期待下一次<strong>gzruby</strong>聚会，2012年1月18日（预计）.
明年见<br />
Really looking forward to the next meeting, planned for <strong>Jan 18, 2012</strong>! See you all next year.</p>

<p>Photo by/ 照片提供：<a href="http://www.weibo.com/littlepxy">littlepxy</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing gzruby]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2011/10/11/announcing-gzruby/"/>
    <updated>2011-10-11T11:27:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.gzruby.org/blog/2011/10/11/announcing-gzruby</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After witnessing the success of the <a href="http://techparty.org">GZ Tech Party</a> events and filled with enthusiasm from the great <a href="http://reddotrubyconf.com">Red Dot Ruby Conf</a>, some of the ruby developers in Guangzhou decided it was time to start a ruby group for ourselves. A support group, if you will, for developers who have decided to branch out and work with what could still be considered an &#8220;alternative&#8221; language. The few, the proud, the willing!</p>

<p>Since our first meeting with over 20 attendees, <strong>gzruby</strong> has become a welcome event on the Guangzhou tech calendar. We host a variety of people, from die-hard ruby and rails hackers to students interested in new languages. We even have visitors from the Python and Android user groups at times. Mostly, its a chance for smart developers to get together, share war stories, and learn from each other.</p>

<p>There is a great well of talent here in Guangzhou, and the aim of <strong>gzruby</strong> is to provide a place for that talent to grow, to find colleagues, and to make GZ a better place to live and work for all of us.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
